<PISI>
    <Source>
        <Name>HotShots</Name>
        <Homepage>http://thehive.xbee.net/index.php?module=pages&amp;func=display&amp;pageid=31</Homepage>
        <Packager>
            <Name>Ganesh Iyer</Name>
            <Email>iyer.gb.linux@gmail.com</Email>
        </Packager>
        <License>GPLv2</License>
        <PartOf>desktop.misc</PartOf>
        <IsA>app:gui</IsA>
        <Summary>Hotshots is a screenshot tool with some editing features</Summary>
        <Description>Hotshots is a screenshot tool with some editing features. It is particularly suitable for writing documentation (as used in the following chapters) but you can use it to highlight some details on a map image or what ever you want.

Because HotShots is written with Qt, it runs on Windows and Linux (MacOSX isn't tested yet).

Why this name, Hotshots ? Firstly, I'm a fan of Jim Abrahams's film and my second choice was Screen'n Shot but I'm not sure the pun will be perenne.

Current Features:

-Grab current screen, all monitors (in case of multi-monitors configuration), current window or a part of the desktop.
-Save the screenshot in multiple formats (PNG, JPG, BMP, ...).
-Automatically save the screenshot to clipboard, disk or launch the editor tool.
-Automatically scale the screenshot to a given size.
-Use “system” shortcuts to take a screenshot.
-Add automatically some “post-effects” to the screenshot (drop shadow, rotation, border, …).
-Add annotation items (text, arrows, rectable, ...) to the snapshot.
-Can be minimized to system tray and work in background.
-Can be launch at system start-up (Windows).
-Export edited image in multiple formats (PNG, JPG, BMP ...).
-Save/Restore edited image in proprietary format.
-Send image directly to printer or to web service</Description>
        <BuildDependencies>
            <Dependency>libqxt-devel</Dependency>
            <Dependency>qt-devel</Dependency>
        </BuildDependencies>
        <Archive sha1sum="4a3d0bce41b5e4013cb42f2f27ca2d7ed17b5cfa" type="zip">http://sourceforge.net/projects/hotshots/files/2.0.0/HotShots-2.0.0-src.zip</Archive>
    </Source>
    <Package>
        <Name>HotShots</Name>
        <RuntimeDependencies>
            <Dependency>libqxt</Dependency>
            <Dependency>qt</Dependency>
        </RuntimeDependencies>
        <Files>
            <Path fileType="executable">/usr/bin/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="data">/usr/share/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="localedata">/usr/share/hotshots/*</Path>
        </Files>
    </Package>
    <History>
        <Update release="1">
            <Date>2013-12-11</Date>
            <Version>2.0.0</Version>
            <Comment>Initial Release</Comment>
            <Name>Ganesh Iyer</Name>
            <Email>iyer.gb.linux@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
    </History>
</PISI>

<!-- By PiSiDo 2.0.0 -->
