<PISI>
    <Source>
        <Name>taskcoach</Name>
        <Homepage>http://taskcoach.org/</Homepage>
        <Packager>
            <Name>Ganesh Iyer</Name>
            <Email>iyer.gb.linux@gmail.com</Email>
        </Packager>
        <License>GPLv3</License>
        <PartOf>office</PartOf>
        <IsA>app:gui</IsA>
        <Summary>Task Coach is a simple open source todo manager</Summary>
        <Description>The desktop version of Task Coach (Windows, Mac, Linux, BSD) has the following features:

-Creating, editing, and deleting tasks and subtasks.
-Tasks have a subject, description, priority, start date, due date, a completion date and an optional reminder. Tasks can recur on a daily, weekly or monthly basis.
-Tasks can be viewed as a list or as a tree.
-Tasks can be sorted by all task attributes, e.g. subject, budget, budget left, due date, etc.
-Several filters to e.g. hide completed tasks or view only tasks that are due today.
-Tasks can be created by dragging an e-mail message from a mail user agent (Outlook, Thunderbird, Claws Mail, Apple Mail) onto a task viewer.
-Attachments can be added to tasks, notes, and categories by dragging and dropping files, e-mail messages, or URL's onto a task, note or category.
-Task status depends on its subtask and vice versa. E.g. if you mark the last uncompleted subtask as completed, the parent task is automatically marked as completed too.
-Tasks and notes can be assigned to user-defined categories.
-Settings are persistent and saved automatically. The last opened file is loaded automatically when starting Task Coach.
-Tracking time spent on tasks. Tasks can have a budget. Time spent can be viewed by individual effort period, by day, by week, and by month.
-The Task Coach file format (.tsk) is XML.
-Tasks, notes, effort, and categories can be exported to HTML and CSV (comma separated format). Effort can be exported to iCalendar/ICS format as well.
-Tasks, effort, notes, and categories can be printed. When printing, Task Coach prints the information that is visible in the current view, including any filters and sort order.
-Task Coach can be run from a removable medium.
-Tasks and notes can be synchronized via a Funambol server such as My Funambol.</Description>
        <Archive sha1sum="57fb35637c59cf696f9b2aae09acd6c1ad2d3a79" type="targz">http://sourceforge.net/projects/taskcoach/files/taskcoach/Release-1.3.34/TaskCoach-1.3.34.tar.gz</Archive>
    </Source>
    <Package>
        <Name>taskcoach</Name>
        <Files>
            <Path fileType="executable">/usr/bin/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="library">/usr/lib/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="data">/usr/share/applications/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="doc">/usr/share/doc/*</Path>
            <Path fileType="data">/usr/share/pixmaps/*</Path>
        </Files>
        <AdditionalFiles>
            <AdditionalFile target="/usr/share/applications/taskcoach.desktop" permission="0644" group="root" owner="root">taskcoach.desktop</AdditionalFile>
            <AdditionalFile target="/usr/share/pixmaps/taskcoach.png" permission="0644" group="root" owner="root">taskcoach.png</AdditionalFile>
        </AdditionalFiles>
        <RuntimeDependencies>
            <Dependency>wxPython</Dependency>
        </RuntimeDependencies>
    </Package>
    <History>
        <Update release="1">
            <Date>2013-12-13</Date>
            <Version>1.3.34</Version>
            <Comment>Initial Build</Comment>
            <Name>Ganesh Iyer</Name>
            <Email>iyer.gb.linux@gmail.com</Email>
        </Update>
    </History>
</PISI>

<!-- By PiSiDo 2.0.0 -->
